By RentAnAdviser.com
Your challengers are a young
group from Houston
Welcome Beyoncé‚ Lativia‚ Nina‚
Nicky‚ Kelly‚ and Ashley
The Hip Hop Rappin′
′Girls TYME′
I am out that H town
coming coming down
I am coming down‚ drippin′
candy on the ground
H‚ H Town‚ Town‚ I am coming down
Coming‚ coming down‚ dripping
candy on the ground
I know when you were le girls
You dreamt of being in my world
Don′t forget it‚ don′t forget it
Respect that‚ bow down bitches (Crown)
I took some time to live my life
But don′t think I am just his le wife
Don′t get it twisted‚ get it twisted
This my shit‚ bow down bitches
Bow down bitches‚ bow bow
down bitches (Crown)
H Town vicious
H‚ H Town vicious
I am so crown crown‚ bow down bitches
I am out that H‚ town‚
coming coming down
I am coming down‚ drippin′
candy on the ground
H‚ H town town
I am coming down
Coming‚ coming down
Drippin′ candy on the ground
We teach girls to shrink themselves
To make themselves smaller
We say to girls
You can have ambition
But not too much
You should aim to be successful
But not too successful
Otherwise you will threaten the man.
Because I am female
I am expected to aspire to marriage
I am expected to make my life choices
Always keeping in mind that
Marriage is the most important
Now marriage can be a source of
Joy and love and mutual support
But why do we teach girls
to aspire to marriage
And we don′t teach boys the same?
We raise girls to see each
other as competitors
Not for jobs or for accomplishments
Which I think can be a good thing
But for the attention of men
We teach girls that they cannot
be sexual beings
In the way that boys are
Feminist: the person who
believes in the social
Political‚ and economic
equality of the sexes
You wake up‚ flawless
Post up‚ flawless
Ridin′ round in it‚ flawless
Flossin′ on that‚ flawless
This diamond‚ flawless
My diamond‚ flawless
This rock‚ flawless
My rock‚ flawless
I woke up like this
We flawless‚ ladies tell them
Say I look so good tonight
God damn‚ God damn
God damn‚ God damn‚ God damn
Momma taught me good home training
My Daddy taught me how
to love my haters
My sister told me I should
speak my mind
My man made me feel so God damn
fine‚ I am flawless!
You wake up‚ flawless
Post up‚ flawless
Riding round in it‚ flawless
Flossing on that‚ flawless
This diamond‚ flawless
My diamond‚ flawless
This rock‚ flawless
My rock‚ flawless
I woke up like this
We flawless‚ ladies tell them
Say I look so good tonight
God damn‚ God damn
God damn‚ God damn‚ God damn
The Judges give champion
Skeleton Crew 4 Stars
A perfect score
And the challenger Girls
TYME receives‚ 3 stars
Skeleton Crew‚ champions once again
Congratulations‚ we′ll
see you next week
By RentAnAdviser.com